Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection
1923-2019 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG030-07-13
Central Washington University, Athletics Department
122.0 cubic feet 111 letter sized document cases; 5 half letter sized document cases; 3 legal sized document cases; 4 record storage cartons; 14 record center boxes; 7 roll storage boxes, 4 garment storage boxes and 5 oversized boxes Media guides, game programs, news releases, newspaper clippings, photographs, negatives, ephemera, and artifacts in fair condition with noticeable aging to older material
This collection consists of annual reports, media guides, sporting event programs, news releases, newspaper clippings, photographs, negatives, video cassettes, ephemera, and artifacts retained by the Central Washington University's Athletics Department from 1923 to 2023.
Historical Note
The Athletics Department at Central Washington University dates back to 1893 with the introduction of a Physical Culture class at the Washington State Normal School and with the first women’s basketball game played in 1895. Throughout the 1890s and early 1900s, the men’s and women’s basketball teams played local and regional high schools. In 1909 the Normal School hired a part-time athletics coach to manage the growing number of sports teams. Later that same year, the men’s basketball team played Bellingham Normal School (Western Washington University), making it the first inter-collegiate sporting event in the school’s history. The athletics program served as part of the Department of Health and Physical Education until 1983 when it became its own independent department.
The bulk of the material in this collection dates from the late 1960s to the early 1990s. Significant items in the collection include basketball programs during the Dean Nicholson era, team photographs, game scorebooks dating back to 1948, videos of football games during 1990s, women’s basketball games during the early 2000s, championship banners and letter jackets.
Since 2014 most Athletics information is born digital. These electronic materials can be accessed on computers in the archives reading room.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Organized into eleven series: I. Annual reports; II. Media guides; III. Newspaper clipping and news releases IV. Programs; V. Programs, basketball; VI. Scorebooks; VII. Miscellaneous records; VIII. Photographs and negatives; IX. Video cassettes; X. Oversized. XI. Scrapbooks. Alphabetically arranged by subject heading of file folder.
Open to the public for educational research.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University, Athletic Department
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Athletics--United States; College sports--Washington (State)
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Annual Reports, I
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Men, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 5-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 5-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5-7)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6-5)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Annual reports – Sport teams – Women, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 6-8)
- Media Guides, II
  - Media Guides – Baseball / Track, 1984 (Box-folder 7-1)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1985 (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1986 (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1987 (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1988 (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1989 (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Media Guides – Baseball, 1991 (Box-folder 7-7)
  - Media Guides – Football, 2000 (Box-folder 7-8)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1952 (Box-folder 7-9)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1953 (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1964 (Box-folder 7-11)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1965 (Box-folder 7-12)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1966 (Box-folder 7-13)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1967 (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1970 (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Media Guides – Spring sports, 1981 (Box-folder 7-16)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1968 (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1969 (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1971 (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1985 (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1986 (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1988 (Box-folder 8-7)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1989 (Box-folder 8-8)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1990 (Box-folder 8-9)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1991 (Box-folder 8-10)
  - Media Guides – Track and Field, 1992 (Box-folder 8-11)
  - Media Guides – Volleyball, 2000 (Box-folder 8-12)
  - Media Guides – Volleyball, 2001 (Box-folder 8-13)
  - Media Guides – Winter sports, 1974 (Box-folder 8-14)
  - Media Guides – Women’s Basketball, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 8-15)
  - Media Guides – Women’s Soccer, 2000 (Box-folder 8-16)
  - Media Guides – Wrestling, 1975 (Box-folder 8-17)
  - Media Guides – GNAC Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 8-18)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 9-4)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 2000 (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Media Guides – Men’s Basketball, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Media Guides –Women’s Basketball, 1962-2000 (Box-folder 10-4)
  - Newsletter – CWU Football Moms, 2000 (Box-folder 10-5)
- Newspaper Clippings and News Releases, III
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1930s (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971 (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972 (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1973 (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box-folder 11-6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box-folder 11-7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box-folder 11-8)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1977 (Box-folder 11-9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 11-10)
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1970s (Box-folder 11-11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, circa 1980s (Box-folder 11-12)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box-folder 11-13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2001 (Box-folder 11-14)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 2002 (Box-folder 11-15)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 11-16)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1952 (Box-folder 11-17)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1953 (Box-folder 11-18)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1953 (Box-folder 11-19)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, December, 1953 (Box-folder 11-20)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1954 (Box-folder 11-21)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1955 (Box-folder 11-22)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1965 (Box-folder 11-23)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1966 (Box-folder 11-24)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1968-April, 1968 (Box-folder 11-25)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, May, 1968-November, 1968 (Box-folder 11-26)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, December, 1968 (Box-folder 11-27)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1969 (Box-folder 11-28)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1969 (Box-folder 11-29)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1969 (Box-folder 11-30)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, June, 1969-December, 1969 (Box-folder 11-31)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1970 (Box-folder 12-1)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1970 (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1970 (Box-folder 12-3)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1970 (Box-folder 12-4)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, April, 1970 (Box-folder 12-5)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, May, 1970-November, 1970 (Box-folder 12-6)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, December, 1970 (Box-folder 12-7)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1971 (Box-folder 12-8)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1971 (Box-folder 12-9)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1971 (Box-folder 12-10)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, May, 1971-November, 1971 (Box-folder 12-11)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, December, 1971 (Box-folder 12-12)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1972 (Box-folder 12-13)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1972 (Box-folder 12-14)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1972 (Box-folder 12-15)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, May, 1972-December, 1972 (Box-folder 12-16)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1973 (Box-folder 12-17)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1973 (Box-folder 12-18)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1973 (Box-folder 12-19)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, May, 1973-December, 1973 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1974 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, February, 1974 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, March, 1974 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, April, 1974-October, 1974 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, November, 1974 (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, December, 1974 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, January, 1975-April, 1975 (Box-folder 13-8)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Baseball, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13-9)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Cross Country, 1980 (Box-folder 13-10)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Football, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 13-11)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1966 (Box-folder 13-12)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13-13)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 13-14)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13-15)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1973 (Box-folder 13-16)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1974 (Box-folder 13-17)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1975 (Box-folder 13-18)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1976 (Box-folder 13-19)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1977 (Box-folder 13-20)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1979 (Box-folder 13-21)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1980 (Box-folder 13-22)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, 1981 (Box-folder 13-23)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Swimming, Women, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 13-24)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Track and Field, 1975 (Box-folder 13-25)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Track and Field, 1976 (Box-folder 13-26)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Track and Field, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 13-27)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Wrestling, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 13-28)
  - New Releases, 1960 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - New Releases, 1961 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - New Releases, 1962 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - New Releases, January, 1963-September, 1963 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - New Releases, October, 1963-December, 1963 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - New Releases, January, 1964-May, 1964 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - New Releases, June, 1964-December, 1964 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - New Releases, January, 1965-May, 1965 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - New Releases, June, 1965-December, 1965 (Box-folder 14-9)
  - New Releases, January, 1966-April, 1966 (Box-folder 14-10)
  - New Releases, May, 1966-December, 1966 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - New Releases, January, 1967-March, 1967 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - New Releases, June, 1967-December, 1967 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - New Releases, January, 1968-March, 1968 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - New Releases, April, 1968-December, 1968 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - New Releases, 1969 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - New Releases, 1970 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - New Releases, 1971 (Box-folder 15-8)
  - New Releases, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - New Releases, 1989-1997 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - New Releases, 1999 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - New Releases, 2000 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - New Releases – Baseball, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - New Releases – Baseball, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - New Releases – Basketball, Men, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - New Releases – Basketball, Men, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 17-4)
  - New Releases – Golf, 1973-1993 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - New Releases – Swimming, Men, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 17-6)
  - New Releases – Swimming, Women, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - New Releases – Tennis, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - New Releases – Track and Field, Men, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - New Releases – Track and Field, General, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - New Releases – Track and Field, General, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - New Releases – Wrestling, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - New Releases – Wrestling, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 18-7)
- Programs of Sporting Events, IV
  - Programs – A. A. A., Wrestling Championships, 1987 (Box-folder 19-1)
  - Programs – A. A. A., Wrestling Championships, 1988 (Box-folder 19-2)
  - Programs – A. I. A. W., Track and Field Championships, 1976 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - Programs – A. I. A. W., Track and Field Championships, 1977 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Programs – A. I. A. W., Track and Field Championships, 1979 (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Programs – A. I. A. W., Track and Field Championships, 1981 (Box-folder 19-6)
  - Programs – A. I. A. W., Region IX Track and Field Championships, 1981 (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track Meet, 1965 (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One and Two Track Meet, 1966 (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track Meet, 1971 (Box-folder 19-10)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1980 (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1981 (Box-folder 19-12)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1982 (Box-folder 19-13)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1983 (Box-folder 19-14)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1984 (Box-folder 19-15)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1985 (Box-folder 19-16)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1986 (Box-folder 19-17)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1987 (Box-folder 19-18)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1988 (Box-folder 19-19)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1989 (Box-folder 19-20)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1990 (Box-folder 19-21)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1991 (Box-folder 19-22)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1992 (Box-folder 19-23)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., District One Track and Field Championships, 1994 (Box-folder 19-24)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., National Championships Wrestling, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 19-25)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., National Championships Wrestling, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 19-26)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., National Wrestling Tournament, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 19-27)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., Track and Field Championships, 1988 (Box-folder 19-28)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., Track and Field Championships, 1992 (Box-folder 19-29)
  - Programs – N.A.I.A., Track and Field Championships, 1993 (Box-folder 19-30)
  - Programs – N. C. A. A., Track and Field Championships, 1970 (Box-folder 19-31)
  - Programs – N. C. W. S. A., Track and Field Regional Championship, 1975 (Box-folder 19-32)
  - Programs – N. C. W. S. A. and A. I. A. W. Region IX, Track and Field Championships, 1982 (Box-folder 19-33)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1925 (Box-folder 19-34)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1926 (Box-folder 19-35)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1929 (Box-folder 19-36)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1932 (Box-folder 19-37)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1933 (Box-folder 19-38)
  - Programs – Dual Track and Field Meet, 1934 (Box-folder 20-1)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1936 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1937 (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Programs – Tri-Normal Track and Field Meet, 1938 (Box-folder 20-4)
  - Programs – Track and Field Meet, 1940 (Box-folder 20-5)
  - Programs – Washington Intercollegiate Conference Championships, 1941 (Box-folder 20-6)
  - Programs – Washington Intercollegiate Conference Championships, 1948 (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Programs – Washington State Wrestling Tournaments, 1960s (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Programs – Washington State Wrestling Tournaments, 1970s (Box-folder 20-9)
  - Programs – Washington State Wrestling Tournaments, 1980s (Box-folder 20-10)
  - Programs – Wrestling, 1960s (Box-folder 20-11)
  - Programs – Wrestling, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 20-12)
  - Ephemera – Results of Tri-Normal Meets, 1923-1930 (Box-folder 20-13)
  - Ephemera – Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box-folder 20-14)
- Programs for Basketball Games, V
  - Programs – Basketball, 1940s (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1950s (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 21-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21-10)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21-11)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 22-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 22-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 22-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 23-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 23-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 23-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 23-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 23-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 23-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 24-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 24-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, International Basketball Invitation Tournament, 1985 (Box-folder 24-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 24-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, November, 1987-December, 1987 (Box-folder 24-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, January, 1988-February, 1988 (Box-folder 24-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, January, 1989-February, 1989 (Box-folder 24-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, December, 1989-February, 1990 (Box-folder 24-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, December, 1990 (Box-folder 24-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, January, 1991-February, 1991 (Box-folder 24-10)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 24-11)
  - Programs – Basketball, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 24-12)
  - Programs – Basketball Tournaments – Winter Park Rotary, 2001 (Box-folder 24-13)
  - Programs—Football, 1942-1948 (Box-folder 25-1)
  - Programs—Football, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 25-2)
  - Programs—Football, 1971 (Box-folder 25-3)
  - Programs—Football, 1972 (Box-folder 25-4)
  - Programs—Football, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 25-5)
  - Programs—Football, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 25-6)
  - Programs—Football, 1999 (Box-folder 25-7)
  - Programs—Football, 1999 (Box-folder 25-8)
  - Programs—Football, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 25-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1965 (Box-folder 26-1)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1966 (Box-folder 26-2)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1967 (Box-folder 26-3)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1968 (Box-folder 26-4)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1970 (Box-folder 26-5)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1971 (Box-folder 26-6)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1974 (Box-folder 26-7)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1975 (Box-folder 26-8)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1976 (Box-folder 26-9)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1977 (Box-folder 26-10)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1978 (Box-folder 26-11)
  - Programs – Basketball, N.A.I.A. Tournament, 1979 (Box-folder 26-12)